When I think about the people that I was aligned with, that I was in the same industry with
in Los Angeles, so many of them, their entire identity is based on being whack people pretending
to be good people. Like that's, that's the whole shtick. And so in this time where we are stepping
into an inability to avoid truth and a confronting of reality, you're going to see your faves really
show themselves and you're going to be shocked because they're not going to have the cover
of pretense anymore because that's not the vibe. Being good is no longer even valuable to the powers
that be. So the folks who are faking the funk aren't going to keep faking it anymore. And those who have
built their entire identity off of being fake good are about to be real whack. I hope you're ready for
it. I got out of there. Thank the Lord. However, so many are stuck and the people who are actually
good folks, but have aligned themselves inextricably to this terrible industry. I worry for you and I
hope that you will have the courage to step out and to step forward and to step into something better
for you and for the world. I think you'll find, sir, that there will come a time when black people
wake up and become intellectually independent enough to think for themselves as other humans
are intellectually independent enough to think for themselves. Then the black man will think like a black
man and he will feel for other black people. And this new thinking and feeling will cause black people to
stick together.